gym-pact.com 2015-04-28

# Privacy Policy | Pact

## PRIVACY POLICY

Last Updated: 14 July 2014

### Service.

Pact, Inc. (Pact) owns and operates the website [http://www.pactapp.com](http://www.pactapp.com/) (the Site). Pact also develops, operates and distributes certain software applications (Apps), which include hosted applications and applications for mobile devices. The Site and the Apps, together with all content, forums, information sharing functions (including the ability to post User-generated content, User Content), tools, transactions and other services available at the Site or by using the Apps, are collectively referred to as the Service.

The following policy explains how Pact may collect, use and disseminate information obtained from Users of the Service. Capitalized terms used herein without definition will have the same meanings as defined in the Terms of Service applicable to the Site, Apps and Service, which are available at <http://www.pactapp.com/legal/tos>.

### Information Collected.

When you visit the Site, access an App or otherwise use the Service, web servers collect general information about your visit (such as, for example, traffic data like time, date and the address of the website from which you entered the Site), which is stored as anonymous, aggregate data. Pact also collects more specific information about you and your use of the Service (such as, for example, demographic data, profile data and frequency or duration of use). Collecting such data (Traffic Data) may entail the use of software programs, web beacons, pixel tags, cookies, IP addresses or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. 

At your election ("opt-in"), you may elect to register, thereby gaining access to additional aspects of the Service (such as, for example, ability to use Apps and make Pacts). When you do so, our registration process may require you to specify a username and password, and to provide your name, address, zip code, legitimate electronic mail address and certain additional information (such as, for example, your preferred contact method, health and fitness goals and goods and services that may be of interest); in order to obtain certain aspects of the Service, you may also elect to provide access information related to your accounts at social networking sites (such as, for example, Facebook); and in order to obtain certain Transaction services (such as, for example, in order to establish Pacts), you will be required to provide valid credit card or verified PayPal account information for billing and Rewards purposes (collectively, Registration Data).

Apps may collect and transmit to Pact information about your location, which is used in connection with your use of the Service.

By identifying yourself through a social networking account, Pact may obtain additional information about your corresponding profile (to the extent permitted by the terms, conditions and functions of that social networking site).

### Children.

If Pact becomes aware that a person under 13 has provided personally identifiable information, it will take reasonable steps to remove such information and terminate the respective account.

### Use of Information.

Pact uses Traffic Data to help diagnose problems with its web servers, to administer the Site and to analyze User trends and behaviors. Your IP address is not linked to personally identifiable information, but is used to gather broad demographic data and to monitor statistics to improve the Service.

Pact (and certain of its service providers, like payment processors) use Registration Data to deliver certain aspects of the Service to you, to contact you when necessary, to respond to your inquiries for additional information, to provide additional information according to your preferences, to facilitate or process Transactions, and for Pact's other business purposes. Sometimes Registration Data is used to send you information about goods, services, forums and other information and services that are available at the Site or other websites. At your election at any time ("opt-out"), you may choose to stop receiving future communications from Pact (see below).

Pact will use social networking account information only for the purpose of providing the Service to the applicable Client, and Pact will not otherwise attempt to obtain information from (or post information using) such accounts without Client’s permission.

### IP Addresses and Cookies.

Pact uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with its web servers and administer the Site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and to gather demographic information. IP addresses are also used to provide an audit trail regarding use of the Service.

"Cookies" are pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. You may be able to set your web browser to refuse cookies, which in turn may affect your ability to access and use the Service.

At this time, Pact does not utilize cookies to track your activities outside of the Service.

### Do Not Track Policy.

Your browser may offer you a “Do Not Track” option, which allows you to signal to operators of websites and web applications and services (including behavioral advertising services) that you do not wish such operators to track certain of your online activities over time and across different websites. Do not Track signals are set on a browser-by-browser basis, so you must set them on every browser you use if you do not wish to be tracked.

At this time, Pact does not track your online activities outside of the Service. Therefore, setting or releasing your Do Not Track signal does not affect how the Service operates.

For clarity, this is just our Do Not Track Policy. Pact cannot and does not make any promises about how third parties react when you set Do Not Track signals on your browser. In addition, the Do Not Track signal does not apply to the use of information collected prior to such request.

### Sharing of Information.

Currently, Pact will not share personally identifiable information that it obtains from you with any third party for commercial purposes that are not related to the Service. For clarity, Pact and its payment processors share personally identifiable information about you in connection with processing your Transactions. Pact may, however, disclose personally identifiable data if (a) reasonably necessary to perform the Service, (b) authorized by the User, (c) otherwise permitted under the Privacy Policy or (d) Pact reasonably believes that such action is necessary to conform or comply with any legal, regulatory, law enforcement or similar requirement or investigation, to protect or defend the rights or property of Pact or any User or to enforce the Terms of Service.

### California Residents.

Under California Civil Code Section 1798.83 (the "Shine the Light" law), California residents who provide personal information in obtaining products or services from Pact are entitled to request and obtain from us once a calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with other businesses for their own direct marketing uses. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2015 will receive information regarding 2014 sharing activities). If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this information, please submit a written request to:

Pact, Inc. Attn: California/Shine the Light 650 Alabama Street, Suite 202 San Francisco, CA 94110, USA

### Business Transfers.

Pact may also transfer Traffic Data and Registration Data (including personally identifiable information) to any successor to all or substantially all of its business or assets that concerns the Service. In the event of any such transfer, the successor will have all of the rights and be subject to all of the obligations of this Privacy Policy, including, without limitation, the right to modify or replace this Privacy Policy, as provided herein.

### Security.

Information collected by Pact is stored in secure operating environments that are not made generally available to the public. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet or wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, Pact cannot ensure the security of any information you provide, and you do so at your own risk. Once Pact receives your transmission, it will make reasonable efforts to ensure its security on Pact's systems.

### Third Party Connections.

The Service may permit you to access the Service (including downloading Apps) from, and to link from the Service to, and to cause the Service to inter-operate with, other mobile apps, services and websites (including without limitation, to, from and with the mobile apps, services and websites of Site Affiliates). These other mobile apps, services and websites are not under Pact's control. The privacy and security practices of such other mobiles apps, services and websites linked to, from or with the Service are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and Pact is not responsible for the privacy or security practices or the content of such other mobile apps, services or websites.

### Opt-Out.

You may elect to avoid future communications from Pact by selecting the "Unsubscribe" link, which is located at the bottom of every Pact email; provided, Pact reserves the right to send you important information (such as, for example, information about Transactions entered into using the Service or information about changes to this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Service).

Please be advised that your desire to opt-out of future communications will not be effective (nor will your Pacts or your Service account be terminated) simply by deleting Apps from your mobile device. Opting-out becomes effective only by following the process described in the preceding paragraph (and your Pact(s) can only be terminated by following the process described in the applicable Policy and your Service registration and account can only be terminated by following the Terms of Service).

### Non-US Users.

YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO PACT'S PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION IN ACCORDANCE WITH THIS PRIVACY POLICY. YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE TRANSMITTED, STORED AND PROCESSED BY PACT IN THE COUNTRY WHERE IT WAS COLLECTED AND IN THE UNITED STATES. UNITED STATES LAWS REGARDING PROCESSING OF PERSONAL INFORMATION MAY BE LESS STRINGENT THAN THE LAWS IN YOUR COUNTRY.

### Changes.

Pact reserves the right, at its sole discretion, to modify or replace this Privacy Policy, in whole or in part, at any time. Pact will use reasonable efforts to notify you of any material change at least 30 days in advance of the effective date of any change. Change notices will be communicated by postings at the Site, via the Apps or, in the case of Clients, Pact may also attempt to notify Clients by electronic mail. In any case, you should periodically check the Privacy Policy for changes. Continued use of the Service following any such notice of any change to the Privacy Policy shall constitute your acceptance of those changes. Information collected by the Service is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use.

You may correct or otherwise change your Registration Data by contacting Pact, as provided below.

### Contact.

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy or your dealings with the Service, please contact Pact using our members-only contact form at <https://www.pactapp.com/contact/form> or contact us at:

Pact, Inc.  
650 Alabama Street, Suite 202  
San Francisco, CA 94110, USA  
Attn: Privacy Policy
